<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MovieMonth</string>
    <string name="app_title">30 Movies in 30 days </string>
    <string name="Date_1_Header">Day 1</string>
    <string name="Day_1_Desc"> Day 1 \nCitizen Kane : An exploration about power, wealth and the American Dream. This movie was created in 1941. </string>
    <string name="Date_2_Header">Day 2</string>
    <string name="Day_2_Desc">Day 2 \nThe Godfather: This Movie is about the rise to power of the Corleone Family, A crime organization in New York. This movie was created in 1972</string>
    <string name="Date_3_Header">Day 3</string>
    <string name="Day_3_Desc">Day 3 \n Casablanca: A timeless Lovestory set against the Backdrop of World War II. This movie was created in 1942</string>
    <string name="Date_4_Header">Day 4</string>
    <string name="Day_4_Desc">Day 4 \nThe Shawshank Redemption: A heartwarming and inspiring story about hope and redemption set in prision. This Movie was created in 1994.</string>
    <string name="Date_5_Header">Day 5</string>
    <string name="Day_5_Desc">Day 5: \nPulp Fiction: A nonlinear film that explores themes of heroism, villainy and the nature of chaos. This film was released on 1994</string>
    <string name="Date_6_Header">Day 6</string>
    <string name="Day_6_Desc">Day 6: \nInception: A mind-bending science fiction thriller that explores the nature of dreams and reality. This film was released on 2010</string>
    <string name="Date_7_Header">Day 7</string>
    <string name="Day_7_Desc">Day 7: \nInterstellar: A mind-bending science fiction epic that explores the nature of time and Space. This film was released on 2014.</string>
    <string name="Date_8_Header">Day 8</string>
    <string name="Day_8_Desc">Day 8: \nThe Silence of the Lambs: A chilling thriller about an Investigator seeking help from a genius serial killer. This film was released on 1991</string>
    <string name="Date_9_Header">Day 9</string>
    <string name="Day_9_Desc">Day 9: \nFight Club: A provocative and constroversial film that explores consumerism, masculinity, and mental illness. This film was released on 1999.</string>
    <string name="Date_10_Header">Day 10</string>
    <string name="Day_10_Desc">Day 10: \nSeven: A dark and gritty crime thriller that follows two detectives as they hunt a serial killer that follows the Seven Deadly sins. This film was released on 1995. </string>
    <string name="Date_11_Header">Day 11</string>
    <string name="Day_11_Desc">Day 11: \nParasite: A Korean Film that is a dark comedy-thriller that satarizes class inequality and social hiearchy. This film was relead on 2019.</string>
    <string name="Date_12_Header">Day 12</string>
    <string name="Day_12_Desc">Day 12: \nApocalypse Now: A disturbing film about the Vietnam War. This film was relead on 1979.</string>
    <string name="Date_13_Header">Day 13</string>
    <string name="Day_13_Desc">Day 13: \n2001: A Space Odyssey: A mind-bending film about exploration of the past, present and future of humanity. This film was released on 1968.</string>
    <string name="Date_14_Header">Day 14</string>
    <string name="Day_14_Desc">Day 14: \nThe Pianist: A historical drama about a Polish-Jewish pianist who survived the Holocaust. This film was released o 2002.</string>
    <string name="Date_15_Header">Day 15</string>
    <string name="Day_15_Desc">Day 15: \nSeven Samurai: A classic Japanese film about a group of Samurai who defend a village from a group of bandits. This film was released on 1954. </string>
    <string name="Date_16_Header">Day 16</string>
    <string name="Day_16_Desc">Day 16: \nThe Matrix: A science fiction about a computer hacker who discovers the truth about reality. This film was released on 1999.</string>
    <string name="Date_17_Header">Day 17</string>
    <string name="Day_17_Desc">Day 17: \nSpirited Away: A Japanese animated film about a young girl who gets lost in a spirit world. This film was released on 2001. </string>
    <string name="Date_18_Header">Day 18</string>
    <string name="Day_18_Desc">Day 18 \nOldboy: A south Korean revenge thriller that is very disturbing and violent. This film was relead in 2003. </string>
    <string name="Date_19_Header">Day 19</string>
    <string name="Day_19_Desc">Day 19 \nNo Country for Old Men: A hunter stumbles upon a drug deal gone wrong and becomes a target of a ruthless killer. This film was released on 2007.</string>
    <string name="Date_20_Header">Day 20</string>
    <string name="Day_20_Desc">Day 20 \nSchindlers List: A German businessman saves the lives of hundreds of Jews during the Holocaust. This film was released on 1993.</string>
    <string name="Date_21_Header">Day 21</string>
    <string name="Day_21_Desc">Day 21 \nOn The Job: A gritty crime thriller that exposes the dark underbelly of the Philippine politics and the criminal justice system. This film was released on 2013.</string>
    <string name="Date_22_Header">Day 22</string>
    <string name="Day_22_Desc">Day 22 \nBatch 81: A coming of age film about a group of college students and their experiences while joining a fraternity. This film was released on 1982. </string>
    <string name="Date_23_Header">Day 23</string>
    <string name="Day_23_Desc">Day 23 \nMaynila: Sa Kuko ng mga Liwanag: A drama about a young man who moves to Manila to search for his long lost lover. This film was released in 1975.</string>
    <string name="Date_24_Header">Day 24</string>
    <string name="Day_24_Desc">Day 24 \nInsiang: A drama about a young woman who is forced to become a prostiture. This film was released in 1976.</string>
    <string name="Date_25_Header">Day 25</string>
    <string name="Day_25_Desc">Day 25 \nMetro Manila: A gripping drama about a man who moves to the city to escape powerty and ends up in the criminal underworld. This film was released in 2013. </string>
    <string name="Date_26_Header">Day 26</string>
    <string name="Day_26_Desc">Day 26 \nFeng Shui: A horror film about a mysterious Chinese artifact that brings wealth and misfortune to its owner. This film was released in 2004.</string>
    <string name="Date_27_Header">Day 27</string>
    <string name="Day_27_Desc">Day 27 \nHeneral Luna: A historical biopic about General Antonio Luna, a military strategist during the Philippine-American War. This film was reeased in 2015.</string>
    <string name="Date_28_Header">Day 28</string>
    <string name="Day_28_Desc">Day 28 \nManila Kingpin: The Asiong Salonga Story: A biographical film about the notorious gangster Asion Salonga.</string>
    <string name="Date_29_Header">Day 29</string>
    <string name="Day_29_Desc">Day 29 \nHimala: A drama about a young girl who claims to have seen the Vigin Mary. This film was released in 1982.</string>
    <string name="Date_30_Header">Day 30</string>
    <string name="Day_30_Desc">Day 30 \nMagnifico: A drama about a poor young boy who strives to make a difference in the lives of those around him. This film was released in 2003.</string>

</resources>